A Guide to the Faulkner Family Papers, 1737-1754
Virginia Historical Society
- Volumes added in 1986. 1792-1893
  - Charles James Faulkner (1847-1929), "Boydville," Martinsburg, W. Va.
    - Claim book, 1872-1892
      Concerns Faulkner and Faulkner, Martinsburg, W. Va., covering the law practice of Charles James Faulkner and Elisha Boyd Faulkner.
    - Scrapbook, 1876-1893
      Contains newspaper clippings concerning Charles James Faulkner's career in the U.S. Senate.